A man was left with a $1 bill after his 6 -year -old son ordered a virtual buffet of
food from several restaurants last weekend.
This led to a string of unexpected deliveries and maybe a starring role in an
advertisement campaign.
This led to a string of deliveries and maybe a starring role in an advertisement
campaign. Keith Stonehouse said the food piled up quickly at his home Saturday night
after he let his son use his cell phone to play a before bed.
Keith Stonehouse said the food piled up quickly at his home Saturday night after he
let his son use his cell phone to play a game before bed.
He said the youngster instead used his father's online food ordering account to
order food from one restaurant after another.
boy's mother, Kristin Stonehouse, said that the online food app has reached out to
the family and offered them a $1,000 gift card.
The boy's mother, Kristin Stonehouse,
said that the online food app has reached out to the family and offered them a $1
,000 gift card.
The boy's mother, Kristin Stonehouse, said that the online food app has reached out
to the family and offered them a $1,000 gift card.
The company also is considering using the family in an online promotional campaign.